exams88.in 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Exams88

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Exams88.in collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the **www.exams88.in** website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Exams88.in.

 **Protect Our visitor Information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

 **We Do Not Share Any Personal Information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

 **Changes to this privacy policy**

Exams88.in has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

 **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

If You have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy you can contact us **[Click Here](http://www.exams88.in/contact-us/)**
